buffer.com 2019-12-30

# Legal Policies and Procedures | Buffer

See the steps we take to ensure your privacy and protection with Buffer

## About

We are committed to our users’ rights to privacy. We promise to share transparently all aspects of how the Buffer product and website work in regards to privacy, terms, and personal data, and we are in full support of efforts to ensure your protection online. 

The following is a collection of information and resources to help answer any questions you have about your experience with Buffer. We’re grateful for your interest and proud to have you as a part of our community!

## Privacy Policy

 _Last updated: July 29, 2019_

Buffer provides this Privacy Policy to inform you of our policies and procedures regarding the collection, use, protection, and disclosure of Personal Information received from your use of this website, located at [https://buffer.com](https://buffer.com/) (“Site”), as well as all related websites including our subdomains at [https://reply.buffer.com](https://reply.buffer.com/) and [https://analyze.buffer.com](https://analyze.buffer.com/), applications, browser extensions, and other services provided by us (collectively, together with the Site, our “Service”), and in connection with our customer, vendor, and partner relationships. This Privacy Policy also tells you about your rights and choices with respect to your Personal Information, and how you can reach us to update your contact information or get answers to questions you may have about our privacy practices.

In addition to the activities described in this Privacy Policy, we may process Personal Information on behalf of our commercial customers when they use the Service. We process such Personal Information as a data processor of our commercial customers, which are the entities responsible for the data processing. To understand how a commercial customer processes your Personal Information, please refer to that customer’s privacy policy.

Registration with, use of, and access to the Service is subject to this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use located at <https://buffer.com/legal#terms>. All terms not defined in this Privacy Policy will have the meanings set forth in the Buffer Terms of Use.

 **Click on one of the links below to obtain more information in the listed section:**

  1.  **Personal Information We May Collect**
  2.  **Personal Information Provided by You**
    1.  **Personal Information Collected from Connected Social Media Accounts**
    2.  **Personal Information Automatically Obtained from Your Interactions with the Service**
  3.  **How We May Use Your Personal Information**
  4.  **How We Share Your Personal Information**
  5.  **How We Protect Your Personal Information**
  6.  **Your Rights and Choices**
  7.  **Data Transfers**
  8.  **Children’s Privacy**
  9.  **Updates to this Privacy Policy**
  10.  **Your California Privacy Rights**
  11.  **How to Contact Us**

### 1\. Personal information we may collect

For the purpose of this Privacy Policy, “Personal Information” means any information relating to an identified or identifiable individual. We obtain Personal Information relating to you from various sources described below.

Where applicable, we indicate whether and why you must provide us with your Personal Information, as well as the consequences of failing to do so. If you do not provide Personal Information when requested, you may not be able to benefit from our Service if that information is necessary to provide you with the service or if we are legally required to collect it.

### 2\. Personal information provided by you

 **Registration**  
If you desire to have access to certain restricted sections of the Site or request to receive marketing materials, you may be required to become a registered user, and to submit the following types of Personal Information to Buffer: your name, email address, phone number, full user name, password, city, and time zone.

 **Customer Support**  
We may collect information through your communications with our customer support team or other communications that you may send us and their contents.

 **Making a Purchase**  
When you make payments through the Service, you will need to provide Personal Information such as your credit card number and billing address.

 **Social Media**  
In order to allow you to post to your social media platforms, we may ask you to provide your username, account ids, social handle, timezones, and email address.

 **Other**  
We may also collect your contact details when you provide them in the context of our customer, vendor, and partner relationships.

### 2a. Personal Information Collected from Connected Social Media Accounts

If you connect your third party social media account to your Buffer account, we may collect certain information stored in your social media account such as:

 **Facebook**  
Buffer may allow you to connect a Facebook page or profile to your Buffer account, in which case we will access certain information from Facebook regarding your account. In particular, we may collect profile image, display name, username / page ID or profile ID, access tokens, sent posts. This includes the content of your post and engagement data (such as click rates, likes, re-shares, impressions, as well as general engagement counts), to the extent permitted by applicable law. This data will only be used by Buffer to provide you with the Service you expect and will not be shared with any third parties.

 **Twitter**  
Buffer may allow you to connect a Twitter profile to your Buffer account, in which case we will access certain information from Twitter regarding your account. In particular, we may collect profile image, display name, username / profile ID, access tokens, and sent posts. This includes the content of your post and engagement data (such as click rates, likes, retweets, re-shares, impressions, as well as general engagement counts), to the extent permitted by applicable law. This data will only be used by Buffer to provide you with the Service you expect and will not be shared with any third parties.

 **Instagram**  
Buffer may allow you to connect an Instagram profile to your Buffer account, in which case we will access certain information from Instagram regarding your account. In particular, we may collect profile image, display name, username / profile ID, access tokens, and sent posts. This includes the content of your post and engagement data (such as click rates, likes, re-shares, impressions, as well as general engagement counts), to the extent permitted by applicable law. This data will only be used by Buffer to provide you with the Service you expect and will not be shared with any third parties.

 **Pinterest**  
Buffer may allow you to connect a Pinterest page or profile to your Buffer account, in which case we will access certain information from Pinterest regarding your account. In particular, we may collect profile image, display name, username / profile ID, access tokens, sent posts, and profile boards. This includes the content of your post and engagement data (such as click rates, likes, re-shares, re-pins, impressions, as well as general engagement counts), to the extent permitted by applicable law. This data will only be used by Buffer to provide you with the Service you expect and will not be shared with any third parties.

 **LinkedIn**  
Buffer may allow you to connect a LinkedIn profile to your Buffer account, in which case we will access certain information from LinkedIn regarding your account. In particular,  
we may collect profile image, display name, username / profile ID, access tokens, and sent posts. This includes the content of your post and engagement data (such as click rates, likes, re-shares, impressions, as well as general engagement counts), to the extent permitted by applicable law. This data will only be used by Buffer to provide you with the Service you expect and will not be shared with any third parties.

 **Google+**  
Buffer may allow you to connect a Google+ page or profile to your Buffer account, in which case we will access certain information from Google regarding your account. In particular, we may collect profile image, display name, username / profile ID, access tokens, and sent posts. This includes the content of your post and engagement data (such as click rates, likes, re-shares, impressions, as well as general engagement counts), to the extent permitted by applicable law. This data will only be used by Buffer to provide you with the Service you expect and will not be shared with any third parties.

Additionally, if you connect **Twitter** , **Facebook** , or **Instagram** when utilizing **Buffer Reply** we may collect: profile image, display name, username / page ID, access tokens, sent or received comment text and sent or received private message text.

Additionally, if you connect **Twitter** , **Facebook** , or **Instagram** when utilizing **Buffer Analyze** we may collect: profile image, display name, username / handle, access tokens, social accounts insights data and social accounts demographic data, sent tweets, social account’s followers count, social account’s insights data and social account’s audience data.

### 2b. Personal Information Automatically Obtained from Your Interactions with the Service

 **Log Data**  
When you use our Service, our servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website (“Log Data”). This Log Data may include information such as your IP address, browser type or the domain from which you are visiting, the web-pages you visit, the search terms you use, and any advertisements on which you click.

 **Cookies and Similar Technologies**  
Like many websites, we also use “cookie” technology to collect additional website usage data and to improve the Site and our Service. A cookie is a small data file that we transfer to your computer’s hard disk. A session cookie enables certain features of the Site and our service and is deleted from your computer when you disconnect from or leave the Site. A persistent cookie remains after you close your browser and may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to the Site. Persistent cookies can be removed by following your web browser help file directions. Most Internet browsers automatically accept cookies. Buffer may use both session cookies and persistent cookies to better understand how you interact with the Site and our Service, to monitor aggregate usage by our users and web traffic routing on the Site, and to improve the Site and our Service.

We may also automatically record certain information from your device by using various types of technology, including “clear gifs” or “web beacons.” This automatically collected information may include your IP address or other device address or ID, web browser and/or device type, the web pages or sites that you visit just before or just after you use the Service, the pages or other content you view or otherwise interact with on the Service, and the dates and times that you visit, access, or use the Service. We also may use these technologies to collect information regarding your interaction with email messages, such as whether you opened, clicked on, or forwarded a message, to the extent permitted under applicable law.

You can instruct your browser, by editing its options, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the websites you visit. Please note that if you delete, or choose not to accept, cookies from the Service, you may not be able to utilize the features of the Service to their fullest potential.

 **Do Not Track**  
Buffer does not process or respond to web browsers’ “do not track” signals or other similar transmissions that indicate a request to disable online tracking of users who use our Service.

 **Third Party Web Beacons and Third Party Buttons**  
We may display third-party content on the Service, including third-party advertising. Third-party content may use cookies, web beacons, or other mechanisms for obtaining data in connection with your viewing of the third party content on the Service. Additionally, we may implement third party buttons, such as Facebook “share” buttons, that may function as web beacons even when you do not interact with the button. Information collected through third-party web beacons and buttons is collected directly by these third parties, not by Buffer. Please consult such third party’s data collection, use, and disclosure policies for more information.

 **Links to Other Websites**  
Our Site contains links to other websites. The fact that we link to a website is not an endorsement, authorization or representation of our affiliation with that third party. We do not exercise control over third party websites. These other websites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit Personal Information from you. Other sites follow different rules regarding the use or disclosure of the Personal Information you submit to them. We are not responsible for the content, privacy and security practices, and policies of third-party sites or services to which links or access are provided through the Service. We encourage you to read the privacy policies or statements of the other websites you visit.

### 3\. How we may use your personal information

We may use the Personal Information we obtain about you to:

  * create and manage your account, provide our Service, process payments, and respond to your inquiries;
  * manage account authentication such as two-factor authentication
  * communicate with you to verify your account and for informational and operational purposes, such as account management, customer service, or system maintenance, including by periodically emailing you service-related announcements;
  * tailor our Service (e.g., we may use cookies and similar technologies to remember your preferences);
  * publish your content, comments or messages on social media platforms;
  * provide tailored advertising, for Buffer services, via Google AdWords;
  * aggregate your Personal Information for analytical purposes;
  * provide customer support;
  * operate, evaluate and improve our business (including by developing new products and services; managing our communications; determining the effectiveness of our advertising; analyzing how the Service is being accessed and used; tracking performance of the Service; debugging the Service; facilitating the use of our Service);
  * send you marketing communications about products, services, offers, programs and promotions of Buffer, and affiliated companies;
  * ensure the security of our Service;
  * manage our customer, service provider and partner relationships;
  * enforce our agreements related to our Service and our other legal rights; and
  * comply with applicable legal requirements, industry standards and our policies.

 **If you are located in the European Economic Area, we may process your Personal Information for the above purposes when:**

  * you have consented to the use of your Personal Information, For example, we may seek to obtain your consent for our uses of cookies or similar technologies, or to send you marketing communications.
  * we need your Personal Information to provide you with services and products requested by you, or to respond to your inquiries,
  * we have a legal obligation to use your Personal Information, or
  * we have a legitimate interest in using your Personal Information. In particular, we have a legitimate interest in using your Personal Information to ensure and improve the safety, security, and performance of our Service, to anonymize Personal Information and carry out data analyses.

### 4\. How we share personal information

We may disclose the Personal Information we collect about you as described below or otherwise disclosed to you at the time the data is collected, including with:

 **Social Media Platforms**  
Our primary purpose for using information is to publish your content on social platforms, allow you to track metrics for analytical purposes, and engage with customers through public replies and conversations (direct messages or “DMs”). We may allow you to link your account on Buffer with an account on a third party social network platform, such as Twitter or Facebook, and to transfer your information to and from the applicable third party platform. Once you share your content to a social media platform, its use will be governed by that platform’s privacy policy.

 **Service Providers**  
We engage certain trusted third parties to perform functions and provide services to us, including hosting and maintenance, error monitoring, debugging, performance monitoring, billing, customer relationship, database storage and management, and direct marketing campaigns. We may share your Personal Information with these third parties, but only to the extent necessary to perform these functions and provide such services. We also require these third parties to maintain the privacy and security of the Personal Information they process on our behalf.

 **Compliance with Laws and Law Enforcement**  
Buffer cooperates with government and law enforcement officials or private parties to enforce and comply with the law. To the extent permitted under applicable law, we may disclose any information about you to government or law enforcement officials or private parties as we believe is necessary or appropriate to investigate, respond to, and defend against claims, for legal process (including subpoenas), to protect the property and rights of Buffer or a third party, to protect Buffer against liability, for the safety of the public or any person, to prevent or stop any illegal, unethical, fraudulent, abusive, or legally actionable activity, to protect the security or integrity of the Service and any equipment used to make the Service available, or to comply with the law.

 **Business Transfers**  
Buffer may sell, transfer or otherwise share some or all of its assets, including Personal Information, in connection with a merger, acquisition, reorganization, sale of assets, or similar transaction, or in the event of insolvency or bankruptcy. You will have the opportunity to opt out of any such transfer if the new entity’s planned processing of your information differs materially from that set forth in this Privacy Policy.

 **Other Third Parties**  
We may share Personal Information with our headquarters and affiliates, and business partners to whom it is reasonably necessary or desirable for us to disclose your data for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy. We may also make certain non-Personal Information available to third parties for various purposes, including for business or marketing purposes or to assist third parties in understanding our users’ interest, habits, and usage patterns for certain programs, content, services, advertisements, promotions, and functionality available through the Service.

### 5\. How we protect personal information

Buffer is very concerned about safeguarding the confidentiality of your Personal Information. We employ administrative and electronic measures designed to appropriately protect your Personal Information against accidental or unlawful destruction, accidental loss, unauthorized alteration, unauthorized disclosure or access, misuse, and any other unlawful form of processing of the Personal Information in our possession. Please be aware that no security measures are perfect or impenetrable. We cannot guarantee that information about you will not be accessed, viewed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any of our administrative, physical, and electronic safeguards, subject to requirements under applicable law to ensure or warrant information security.

We will make any legally-required disclosures of any breach of the security, confidentiality, or integrity of your unencrypted electronically stored Personal Information to you via email or conspicuous posting on our Site in the most expedient time possible and without unreasonable delay, consistent with (i) the legitimate needs of law enforcement or (ii) any measures necessary to determine the scope of the breach and restore the reasonable integrity of the data system , and any other disclosures that may be required under applicable law.

We also take measures to delete your Personal Information or keep it in a form that does not permit identifying you when this information is no longer necessary for the purposes for which we process it, unless we are required by law to keep this information for a longer period. When determining the retention period, we take into account various criteria, such as the type of products and services requested by or provided to you, the nature and length of our relationship with you, possible re-enrollment with our products or services, the impact on the services we provide to you if we delete some information from or about you, mandatory retention periods provided by law and the statute of limitations.

### 6\. Your rights and choices

If you decide at any time that you no longer wish to receive such marketing communications from us, please follow the unsubscribe instructions provided in any of the communications. You may also opt out from receiving commercial email from us by sending your request to us by email at [hello@buffer.com](mailto:hello@buffer.com). Please be aware that, even after you opt out from receiving commercial messages from us, you will continue to receive administrative messages from us regarding the Service.

In certain jurisdictions you have the right to request access and receive information about the Personal Information we maintain about you, to update and correct inaccuracies in your Personal Information, to restrict or object to the processing of your Personal Information, to have the information blocked, anonymized or deleted, as appropriate, or to exercise your right to data portability to transfer your Personal Information to another company. Those rights may be limited in some circumstances by local law requirements. In addition to the above-mentioned rights, you also have the right to lodge a complaint with a competent supervisory authority subject to applicable law.

Where required by law, we obtain your consent for the processing of certain Personal Information collected by cookies or similar technologies, or used to send you direct marketing communications, or when we carry out other processing activities for which consent may be required. If we rely on consent for the processing of your Personal Information, you have the right to withdraw it at any time and free of charge. When you do so, this will not affect the lawfulness of the processing before your consent withdrawal.

To update your preferences, ask us to remove your information from our mailing lists, delete your account or submit a request to exercise your rights under applicable law, please contact us as specified in the “How to Contact Us” section below.

### 7\. Data transfers

Buffer is based in the United States. Personal Information that we collect may be transferred to, and stored at, any of our affiliates, partners or service providers which may be inside or outside the European Economic Area (“EEA”) and Switzerland, including the United States. By submitting your personal data, you agree to such transfers. Your Personal Information may be transferred to countries that do not have the same data protection laws as the country in which you initially provided the information. When we transfer or disclose your Personal Information to other countries, we will protect that information as described in this Privacy Policy.

 **Individuals Located in the EEA or Switzerland**  
If you are located in the European Economic Area (“EEA”), the United Kingdom, or Switzerland, we comply with applicable legal requirements for the transfer of Personal Information to countries outside of the EEA, the United Kingdom, and/or Switzerland. In particular, Buffer has filed its certification of adherence to the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework and the Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework as set forth by the Department of Commerce and the European Commission, and the Swiss Federal Data Protection and Information Commissioner, respectively, with respect to the processing of certain Personal Information transferred from the EEA, the United Kingdom and Switzerland to Buffer. For additional details on our compliance with the EU-US privacy Shield Framework and the Swiss-US Privacy Shield Framework please visit: https://buffer.com/privacy-shield. Buffer has certified to the Department of Commerce that it adheres to the Privacy Shield Principles. If there is any conflict between the terms in this privacy policy and the Privacy Shield Principles, the Privacy Shield Principles shall govern. To learn more about the Privacy Shield program, and to view our certification, please visit <https://www.privacyshield.gov/>. In addition, we may enter into Standard Contractual Clauses issued by the European Commission with our commercial customers where appropriate.

### 8\. Children's privacy

The Site is not directed to persons under 16. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided us with Personal Information without their consent, he or she should contact us at [hello@buffer.com](mailto:hello@buffer.com). We do not knowingly collect Personal Information from children under 16. If we become aware that a child under 16 has provided us with Personal Information, we will delete such information from our files.

### 9\. Updates to this Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy may be updated from time to time for any reason; each version will apply to information collected while it was in place. We will notify you of any modifications to our Privacy Policy by posting the new Privacy Policy on our Site and indicating the date of the latest revision. You are advised to consult this Privacy Policy regularly for any changes.

In the event that the modifications materially alter your rights or obligations hereunder, we will make reasonable efforts to notify you of the change. For example, we may send a message to your email address or generate a pop-up or similar notification when you access the Service for the first time after such material changes are made. Your continued use of the Service after the revised Privacy Policy has become effective indicates that you have read, understood and agreed to the current version of this Privacy Policy.

### 10\. Your California privacy rights

Residents of California have the right to request a disclosure describing what types of personal information we have shared with third parties for their direct marketing purposes, and with whom we have shared it, during the preceding year. You may request a copy of that disclosure by contacting us at [hello@buffer.com](mailto:hello@buffer.com).

### 11\. How to contact us

Buffer Inc. is the entity responsible for the processing of your Personal Information. If you have any questions or comments regarding this Privacy Policy, or if you would like to exercise your rights to your Personal Information, you may contact us by emailing us at [hello@buffer.com](mailto:hello@buffer.com) or by writing to us at:

Buffer Inc  
2443 Fillmore St #380-7163  
San Francisco, CA 94115

This Privacy Policy is effective as of **August 6, 2018.**

If you have any thoughts or questions about this Privacy Policy please [let us know](mailto:hello@buffer.com).

## Terms of Use

 _Last updated: December 18, 2017_

Welcome, and thank you for your interest in Buffer, Inc. (“ **Buffer** ,” “ **we** ,” or “ **us** ”) and our website at [buffer.com](http://buffer.com/), along with our related websites, networks, applications, mobile applications, and other services provided by us (collectively, the “Service”). These Terms of Service are a legally binding contract between you and Buffer regarding your use of the Service.

### Please read the following terms carefully

BY CLICKING “I ACCEPT,” OR BY DOWNLOADING, INSTALLING, OR OTHERWISE ACCESSING OR USING THE SERVICE, YOU AGREE THAT YOU HAVE READ AND UNDERSTOOD, AND, AS A CONDITION TO YOUR USE OF THE SERVICE, YOU AGREE TO BE BOUND BY, THE FOLLOWING TERMS AND CONDITIONS, INCLUDING BUFFER’S PRIVACY POLICY AND ANY ADDITIONAL TERMS AND POLICIES BUFFER MAY PROVIDE FROM TIME TO TIME (TOGETHER, THESE "TERMS"). If you are not eligible, or do not agree to the Terms, then you do not have our permission to use the Service. YOUR USE OF THE SERVICE, AND BUFFER’S PROVISION OF THE SERVICE TO YOU, CONSTITUTES AN AGREEMENT BY BUFFER AND BY YOU TO BE BOUND BY THESE TERMS.

Please read the Buffer Privacy Policy (<https://buffer.com/privacy>) carefully for information relating to our collection, use, storage, disclosure of your personal information. The Buffer Privacy Policy is incorporated by this reference into, and made a part of, these Terms.

### Arbitration notice

Except for certain kinds of disputes described in Section 16, you agree that disputes arising under these Terms will be resolved by binding, individual arbitration, and BY ACCEPTING THESE TERMS, YOU AND BUFFER ARE EACH WAIVING THE RIGHT TO A TRIAL BY JURY OR TO PARTICIPATE IN ANY CLASS ACTION OR REPRESENTATIVE PROCEEDING. YOU AGREE TO GIVE UP YOUR RIGHT TO GO TO COURT to assert or defend your rights under this contract (except for matters that may be taken to small claims court). Your rights will be determined by a NEUTRAL ARBITRATOR and NOT a judge or jury. (See Section 16).

### 1\. Buffer Service Overview

The Service provides a social media management tool that enables users to release posts on social platforms at a scheduled time, in addition to other design and analytics tools to help bolster users’ social media content.

### 2\. Eligibility

You must be at least [18] years old to use the Service. By agreeing to these Terms, you represent and warrant to us that: (a) you are at least [18] years old; (b) you have not previously been suspended or removed from the Service; and (c) your registration and your use of the Service is in compliance with any and all applicable laws and regulations. If you are an entity, organization, or company, the individual accepting these Terms on your behalf represents and warrants that they have authority to bind you to these Terms and references to you herein (and all of your obligations hereunder) will refer to such entity and any individual using the Service on such entity’s behalf.

### 3\. Accounts and Registration

To access most features of the Service, you must register for an account. When you register for an account, you may be required to provide us with some information about yourself, such as your name, email address, or other contact information. You agree that the information you provide to us is accurate and that you will keep it accurate and up-to-date at all times. When you register, you will be asked to provide a password. You are solely responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your account and password, and you accept responsibility for all activities that occur under your account. If you believe that your account is no longer secure, then you must immediately notify us at [hello@buffer.com](mailto:hello@buffer.com).

### 4\. General Payment Terms

Premium features of the Service will require you to pay fees upon registering for the applicable premium service. Before you pay any fees, you will have an opportunity to review and accept the fees that you will be charged. All fees are in U.S. Dollars and are non-refundable. Fees vary based on the plan, with different pricing schemes for individual users and organizations.

 **4.1 Price**  
Buffer reserves the right to determine pricing for the Service. Buffer will make reasonable efforts to keep pricing information published on the website up to date. We encourage you to check our website periodically for current pricing information, located here: <https://buffer.com/pricing>. Buffer may change the fees for any feature of the Service, including additional fees or charges, if Buffer gives you advance notice of changes before they apply. Buffer, at its sole discretion, may make promotional offers with different features and different pricing to any of Buffer’s customers. These promotional offers, unless made to you, will not apply to your offer or these Terms.

 **4.2 Authorization**  
You authorize Buffer to charge all sums for the orders that you make and any level of Service you select as described in these Terms or published by Buffer, to the payment method specified in your account. If you pay any fees with a credit card, Buffer may seek pre-authorization of your credit card account prior to your purchase to verify that the credit card is valid and has the necessary funds or credit available to cover your purchase.

 **4.3 Subscription Service and Cancellation Policy**  
The Service may include automatically recurring payments for periodic charges (“ **Subscription Service** ”). If you activate a Subscription Service, you authorize Buffer to periodically charge, on a going-forward basis and until cancellation of either the recurring payments or your account, all accrued sums on or before the payment due date for the accrued sums. The “ **Subscription Billing Date** ” is the date when you purchase your first subscription to the Service. For information on the “ **Subscription Fee** ”, please see our Pricing page. Your account will be charged automatically on the Subscription Billing Date all applicable fees for the next subscription period. The subscription will continue unless and until you cancel your subscription or we terminate it. You must cancel your subscription before it renews in order to avoid billing of the next periodic Subscription Fee to your account. We will bill the periodic Subscription Fee to the payment method you provide to us during registration (or to a different payment method if you change your payment information). You may cancel the Subscription Service by accessing your account settings at: <https://buffer.com/app/account/receipts> and clicking on the "Cancel Plan" option or by contacting us at: [hello@buffer.com](mailto:hello@buffer.com).

 **4.4 Delinquent Accounts**  
Buffer may suspend or terminate access to the Service for any account for which any amount is due but unpaid. In addition to the amount due for the Service, a delinquent account will be charged with fees or charges that are incidental to any chargeback or collection of any the unpaid amount, including collection fees.

### 5\. Licenses

 **5.1 Permission to Use**  
Subject to your complete and ongoing compliance with these Terms, Buffer grants you limited, non-transferable, non-sublicensable, revocable permission to access and use the Service for your personal, internal use during the Term at the level of service for which you have paid all applicable Fees.

 **5.2 Restrictions**  
Except and solely to the extent such a restriction is impermissible under applicable law, you may not: (a) reproduce, distribute, publicly display, or publicly perform the Service; (b) make modifications to the Service; or (c) interfere with or circumvent any feature of the Service, including any security or access control mechanism. If you are prohibited under applicable law from using the Service, you may not use it. You may not use the Service on behalf of any third party, or in a service bureau or similar capacity.

 **5.3 Feedback**  
If you choose to provide input and suggestions regarding problems with or proposed modifications or improvements to the Service (“ **Feedback** ”), then you hereby grant Buffer an unrestricted, perpetual, irrevocable, non-exclusive, fully-paid, royalty-free right to exploit the Feedback in any manner and for any purpose, including to improve the Service and create other products and services.

### 6\. Ownership; Proprietary Rights

The Service is owned and operated by Buffer. The visual interfaces, graphics, design, compilation, information, data, computer code (including source code or object code), products, software, services, templates, and all other elements of the Service (“ **Materials** ”) provided by Buffer are protected by intellectual property and other laws. All Materials included in the Service are the property of Buffer or its third party licensors. Except as expressly authorized by Buffer, you may not make use of the Materials. Buffer reserves all rights to the Materials not granted expressly in these Terms.

### 7\. Third Party Terms

 **7.1 Third Party Services and Linked Websites**  
Buffer provides tools through the Service that enable you to import and export information, including User Content, to and from third party services, including through features that allow you to link your account on Buffer with an account on a third party social network service, such as Twitter or Facebook. By using one of these tools, you agree that Buffer may transfer that information to and from the applicable third party service. Third party services are not under Buffer’s control, and Buffer is not responsible for any third party service’s use of your exported information. The Service may also contain links to third party websites. Linked websites are not under Buffer’s control, and Buffer is not responsible for their content.

 **7.2 Third Party Software**  
The Service may include or incorporate third party software components that are generally available free of charge under licenses granting recipients broad rights to copy, modify, and distribute those components (“ **Third Party Components** ”). Although the Service is provided to you subject to these Terms, nothing in these Terms prevents, restricts, or is intended to prevent or restrict you from obtaining Third Party Components under the applicable third party licenses or to limit your use of Third Party Components under those third party licenses.

### 8\. User Content

 **8.1 User Content Generally**  
Certain features of the Service may permit users to upload content to the Service, including social media posts and other content which may be comprised of messages, reviews, photos, video, images, data, text, and other types of works (“ **User Content** ”) and to publish User Content on the Service. **You retain any copyright and other proprietary rights that you may hold in the User Content that you post to the Service**. _Nevertheless, we need certain permission from you in order to provide the Service_.

 **8.2 Limited License Grant to Buffer**  
By providing User Content to or via the Service, you grant Buffer a worldwide, non-exclusive, royalty-free, fully paid right and license (with the right to sublicense) to host, store, transfer, display, perform, reproduce, modify for the purpose of formatting for display, and distribute your User Content, in whole or in part, in any media formats and through any media channels now known or hereafter developed.

 **8.3 Limited License Grant to Other Users**  
By providing User Content to or via the Service to other users of the Service, you grant those users a non-exclusive license to access and use that User Content as permitted by these Terms and the functionality of the Service.

 **8.4 User Content Representations and Warranties**  
Buffer disclaims any and all liability in connection with User Content. You are solely responsible for your User Content and the consequences of providing User Content via the Service. By providing User Content via the Service, you affirm, represent, and warrant that:

a) you are the creator and owner of the User Content, or have the necessary licenses, rights, consents, and permissions to authorize Buffer and users of the Service to use and distribute your User Content as necessary to exercise the licenses granted by you in this Section, in the manner contemplated by Buffer, the Service, and these Terms;

b) your User Content, and the use of your User Content as contemplated by these Terms, does not and will not: (i) infringe, violate, or misappropriate any third party right, including any copyright, trademark, patent, trade secret, moral right, privacy right, right of publicity, or any other intellectual property or proprietary right; (ii) slander, defame, libel, or invade the right of privacy, publicity or other property rights of any other person; or (iii) cause Buffer to violate any law or regulation; and

c) your User Content could not be deemed by a reasonable person to be objectionable, profane, indecent, pornographic, harassing, threatening, embarrassing, hateful, or otherwise inappropriate.

d) your User Content does not and will not contain Hateful Content, a Threat of Physical Harm, or Harassment

The following serves as a guide to help illustrate generally the types of content that fall within the scope of Buffer’s policy on Hateful Content, Threats of Physical Harm, and Harassment, but is not exhaustive. This Section 8.4(d) does not limit any of our other rights or remedies provided herein. For the avoidance of doubt, your User Content may not include, and Buffer may remove or refuse to publish or promote any User Content that violates the terms or policies of any third party platform with which Buffer’s Services integrate or interoperate.

 **Hateful Content includes:**  
Any statement, image, photograph, or other content that in our sole judgment could be reasonably perceived to harm, threaten, demean, promote the harassment of, promote the intimidation of, or promote the abuse of others for any reason, including by reason of race, gender or gender identity, national origin, sexual orientation, religion, or otherwise.

 **A Threat of Physical Harm includes:**  
Any statement, photograph, advertisement, or other content that in our sole judgment could be reasonably perceived to threaten, advocate, or incite physical harm to or violence against others, including references to current or historical figures or groups that are known for purporting such content, such as the Ku Klux Klan, Nazi Party, and the pke.

 **Harassment includes:**  

    * Revealing someone’s personal information, also known as “doxxing”.
    * Online stalking, and bullying.
    * Wishes for physical harm directed at a person or persons.
    * Incitement of others to any of the previous items.

We reserve the right to suspend or terminate accounts and remove individual posts which contain Hateful Content, a Threat of Physical Harm, or Harassment.

 **We also may suspend or terminate your account if we determine, in our sole discretion, that you are either:**  

    * An organization which has publicly stated or acknowledged that its goals, objectives, positions, or founding tenets include statements or principles that could be reasonably perceived to advocate, encourage, or sponsor Hateful Content, Harassment, or A Threat of Physical Harm.
    * A person or organization that has acted in such a way as could be reasonably perceived to support, condone, encourage, or represent Hateful Content, Harassment, or A Threat of Physical Harm.

Notwithstanding the foregoing, we reserve the right to screen, remove, edit, or block any User Content we find in violation of the Terms or that we find, in our sole discretion to be otherwise objectionable, at our sole discretion.

 **8.5 User Content Disclaimer**  
We are under no obligation to edit or control User Content that you or other users post or publish, and will not be in any way responsible or liable for User Content. Buffer may, however, at any time and without prior notice, screen, remove, edit, or block any User Content that in our sole judgment violates these Terms or is otherwise objectionable. You understand that when using the Service you will be exposed to User Content from a variety of sources and acknowledge that User Content may be inaccurate, offensive, indecent, or objectionable. You agree to waive, and do waive, any legal or equitable right or remedy you have or may have against Buffer with respect to User Content. If notified by a user or content owner that User Content allegedly does not conform to these Terms, we may investigate the allegation and determine in our sole discretion whether to remove the User Content, which we reserve the right to do at any time and without notice. For clarity, Buffer does not permit copyright-infringing activities on the Service.

 **8.6 Monitoring Content**  
Buffer does not control and does not have any obligation to monitor: (a) User Content; (ii) any content made available by third parties; or (iii) the use of the Service by its users. You acknowledge and agree that Buffer reserves the right to, and may from time to time, monitor any and all information transmitted or received through the Service for operational and other purposes. If at any time Buffer chooses to monitor the content, Buffer still assumes no responsibility or liability for content or any loss or damage incurred as a result of the use of content. During monitoring, information may be examined, recorded, copied, and used in accordance with our Privacy Policy.

### 9\. Prohibited Conduct

BY USING THE SERVICE YOU AGREE NOT TO:

  * use the Service for any illegal purpose or in violation of any local, state, national, or international law;
  * violate, or encourage others to violate, any right of a third party, including by infringing or misappropriating any third party intellectual property right;
  * interfere with security-related features of the Service, including by: (i) disabling or circumventing features that prevent or limit use or copying of any content; (ii) reverse engineering or otherwise attempting to discover the source code of any portion of the Service except to the extent that the activity is expressly permitted by applicable law; or (iii) hacking, password “mining” or using any other illegitimate means of interference;
  * modify or create derivatives of any part of the Service;
  * interfere with the operation of the Service or any user’s enjoyment of the Service, including by: (i) uploading or otherwise disseminating any virus, adware, spyware, worm, or other malicious code; (ii) making any unsolicited offer or advertisement to another user of the Service; (iii) collecting personal information about another user or third party without consent; or (iv) interfering with or disrupting any network, equipment, or server connected to or used to provide the Service;
  * perform any fraudulent activity including impersonating any person or entity, claiming a false affiliation, accessing any other Service account without permission, or falsifying your age or date of birth;
  * take action that imposes an unreasonable or disproportionately large load on the infrastructure of the Service of Buffer’s systems or networks, or any systems or networks connected to the Service or Buffer;
  * sell or otherwise transfer the access granted under these Terms or any Materials (as defined in Section 6) or any right or ability to view, access, or use any Materials; or
  * attempt to do any of the acts described in this Section 9 or assist or permit any person in engaging in any of the acts described in this Section 9.

### 10\. Digital Millennium Copyright Act

 **10.1 DMCA Notification**  
We comply with the provisions of the Digital Millennium Copyright Act applicable to Internet service providers (17 U.S.C. §512, as amended). If you have an intellectual property rights-related complaint about material posted on the Service, you may contact our Designated Agent at the following address:

Buffer, Inc.  
ATTN: Legal Department (Copyright Notification)  
2443 Fillmore Street #380-7163  
San Francisco, CA 94115  
Email: [copyright@buffer.com](mailto:copyright@buffer.com)

Any notice alleging that materials hosted by or distributed through the Service infringe intellectual property rights must include the following information:

  * an electronic or physical signature of the person authorized to act on behalf of the owner of the copyright or other right being infringed;
  * a description of the copyrighted work or other intellectual property that you claim has been infringed;
  * a description of the material that you claim is infringing and where it is located on the Service;
  * your address, telephone number, and email address;
  * a statement by you that you have a good faith belief that the use of the materials on the Service of which you are complaining is not authorized by the copyright owner, its agent, or the law; and
  * a statement by you that the above information in your notice is accurate and that, under penalty of perjury, you are the copyright or intellectual property owner or authorized to act on the copyright or intellectual property owner's behalf.

 **10.2 Repeat Infringers**  
It is Buffer’s policy to promptly terminate the accounts of users that are determined by Buffer to be repeat infringers.

### 11\. Modification of these Terms

We reserve the right to change these Terms on a going-forward basis at any time. Please check these Terms periodically for changes. Modifications will become effective upon the earlier of (a) your acceptance of the modified Terms, (b) your use of the Service with actual knowledge of the modified Terms, or (c) thirty (30) days following our publication of the modified Terms through the Service. Except as expressly permitted in this Section 11, these Terms may be amended only by a written agreement signed by authorized representatives of the parties to these Terms. Disputes arising under these Terms will be resolved in accordance with the version of these Terms that was in effect at the time the dispute arose.

### 12\. Term, Termination and Modification of the Service

 **12.1 Term**  
These Terms are effective beginning when you accept the Terms or first download, install, access, or use the Service, and ending when terminated as described in Section 12.2.

 **12.2 Termination**  
If you violate any provision of these Terms, your authorization to access the Service and these Terms automatically terminate. In addition, Buffer may, at its sole discretion, terminate these Terms or your account on the Service, or suspend or terminate your access to the Service, at any time for any reason or no reason, with or without notice. You may terminate your account and these Terms at any time as provided in Section 4.3 or by contacting customer service at [hello@buffer.com](mailto:hello@buffer.com).

 **12.3 Effect of Termination**  
Upon termination of these Terms: (a) your license rights will terminate and you must immediately cease all use of the Service; (b) you will no longer be authorized to access your account or the Service; (c) you must pay Buffer any unpaid amount that was due prior to termination; and (d) all payment obligations accrued prior to termination and Sections 5.3, 6, 12.3, 13, 14, 15, 16 and 17 will survive.

 **12.4 Modification of the Service**  
Buffer reserves the right to modify or discontinue the Service at any time (including by limiting or discontinuing certain features of the Service), temporarily or permanently, without notice to you. Buffer will have no liability for any change to the Service or any suspension or termination of your access to or use of the Service. Premium service fees are not refundable.

### 13\. Indemnity

You are responsible for your use of the Service, and you will defend and indemnify Buffer and its officers, directors, employees, consultants, affiliates, subsidiaries and agents (together, the “Buffer **Entities** ”) from and against every claim brought by a third party, and any related liability, damage, loss, and expense, including reasonable attorneys’ fees and costs, arising out of or connected with: (a) your use of, or misuse of, the Service; (b) your violation of any portion of these Terms, any representation, warranty, or agreement referenced in these Terms, or any applicable law or regulation; (c) your violation of any third party right, including any intellectual property right or publicity, confidentiality, other property, or privacy right; or (d) any dispute or issue between you and any third party. We reserve the right, at our own expense, to assume the exclusive defense and control of any matter otherwise subject to indemnification by you (without limiting your indemnification obligations with respect to that matter), and in that case, you agree to cooperate with our defense of those claims.

### 14\. Disclaimers; No Warranties

THE SERVICE AND ALL MATERIALS AND CONTENT AVAILABLE THROUGH THE SERVICE ARE PROVIDED “AS IS” AND ON AN “AS AVAILABLE” BASIS. BUFFER DISCLAIMS ALL WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND, WHETHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, RELATING TO THE SERVICE AND ALL MATERIALS AND CONTENT AVAILABLE THROUGH THE SERVICE, INCLUDING: (A) ANY IMPLIED WARRANTY OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, TITLE, QUIET ENJOYMENT, OR NON-INFRINGEMENT; AND (B) ANY WARRANTY ARISING OUT OF COURSE OF DEALING, USAGE, OR TRADE. BUFFERDOES NOT WARRANT THAT THE SERVICE OR ANY PORTION OF THE SERVICE, OR ANY MATERIALS OR CONTENT OFFERED THROUGH THE SERVICE, WILL BE UNINTERRUPTED, SECURE, OR FREE OF ERRORS, VIRUSES, OR OTHER HARMFUL COMPONENTS, AND BUFFER DOES NOT WARRANT THAT ANY OF THOSE ISSUES WILL BE CORRECTED.

NO ADVICE OR INFORMATION, WHETHER ORAL OR WRITTEN, OBTAINED BY YOU FROM THE SERVICE OR BUFFER ENTITIES OR ANY MATERIALS OR CONTENT AVAILABLE THROUGH THE SERVICE WILL CREATE ANY WARRANTY REGARDING ANY OF THE BUFFER ENTITIES OR THE SERVICE THAT IS NOT EXPRESSLY STATED IN THESE TERMS. WE ARE NOT RESPONSIBLE FOR ANY DAMAGE THAT MAY RESULT FROM THE SERVICE AND YOUR DEALING WITH ANY OTHER SERVICE USER. YOU UNDERSTAND AND AGREE THAT YOU USE ANY PORTION OF THE SERVICE AT YOUR OWN DISCRETION AND RISK, AND THAT WE ARE NOT RESPONSIBLE FOR ANY DAMAGE TO YOUR PROPERTY (INCLUDING YOUR COMPUTER SYSTEM OR MOBILE DEVICE USED IN CONNECTION WITH THE SERVICE) OR ANY LOSS OF DATA, INCLUDING USER CONTENT.

HOWEVER, BUFFER DOES NOT DISCLAIM ANY WARRANTY OR OTHER RIGHT THAT BUFFER IS PROHIBITED FROM DISCLAIMING UNDER APPLICABLE LAW.

### 15\. Limitation of Liability

TO THE FULLEST EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW, IN NO EVENT WILL THE BUFFER ENTITIES BE LIABLE TO YOU FOR ANY INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, CONSEQUENTIAL OR PUNITIVE DAMAGES (INCLUDING DAMAGES FOR LOSS OF PROFITS, GOODWILL, OR ANY OTHER INTANGIBLE LOSS) ARISING OUT OF OR RELATING TO YOUR ACCESS TO OR USE OF, OR YOUR INABILITY TO ACCESS OR USE, THE SERVICE OR ANY MATERIALS OR CONTENT ON THE SERVICE, WHETHER BASED ON WARRANTY, CONTRACT, TORT (INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE), STATUTE, OR ANY OTHER LEGAL THEORY, AND WHETHER OR NOT ANY BUFFER ENTITY HAS BEEN INFORMED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF DAMAGE.

EXCEPT AS PROVIDED IN SECTION 16.4(iii) AND TO THE FULLEST EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW, THE AGGREGATE LIABILITY OF THE BUFFER ENTITIES TO YOU FOR ALL CLAIMS ARISING OUT OF OR RELATING TO THE USE OF OR ANY INABILITY TO USE ANY PORTION OF THE SERVICE OR OTHERWISE UNDER THESE TERMS, WHETHER IN CONTRACT, TORT, OR OTHERWISE, IS LIMITED TO THE GREATER OF: (A) THE AMOUNT YOU HAVE PAID TO BUFFER FOR ACCESS TO AND USE OF THE SERVICE IN THE 12 MONTHS PRIOR TO THE EVENT OR CIRCUMSTANCE GIVING RISE TO CLAIM; OR (B) $100.

EACH PROVISION OF THESE TERMS THAT PROVIDES FOR A LIMITATION OF LIABILITY, DISCLAIMER OF WARRANTIES, OR EXCLUSION OF DAMAGES IS INTENDED TO AND DOES ALLOCATE THE RISKS BETWEEN THE PARTIES UNDER THESE TERMS. THIS ALLOCATION IS AN ESSENTIAL ELEMENT OF THE BASIS OF THE BARGAIN BETWEEN THE PARTIES. EACH OF THESE PROVISIONS IS SEVERABLE AND INDEPENDENT OF ALL OTHER PROVISIONS OF THESE TERMS. THE LIMITATIONS IN THIS SECTION 15 WILL APPLY EVEN IF ANY LIMITED REMEDY FAILS OF ITS ESSENTIAL PURPOSE.

### 16\. Dispute Resolution and Arbitration

 **16.1 Generally**  
In the interest of resolving disputes between you and Buffer in the most expedient and cost effective manner, and except as described in Section 16.2, you and Buffer agree that every dispute arising in connection with these Terms will be resolved by binding arbitration. Arbitration is less formal than a lawsuit in court. Arbitration uses a neutral arbitrator instead of a judge or jury, may allow for more limited discovery than in court, and can be subject to very limited review by courts. Arbitrators can award the same damages and relief that a court can award. This agreement to arbitrate disputes includes all claims arising out of or relating to any aspect of these Terms, whether based in contract, tort, statute, fraud, misrepresentation, or any other legal theory, and regardless of whether a claim arises during or after the termination of these Terms. YOU UNDERSTAND AND AGREE THAT, BY ENTERING INTO THESE TERMS, YOU AND BUFFER ARE EACH WAIVING THE RIGHT TO A TRIAL BY JURY OR TO PARTICIPATE IN A CLASS ACTION.

 **16.2 Exceptions**  
Despite the provisions of Section 16.1, nothing in these Terms will be deemed to waive, preclude, or otherwise limit the right of either party to: (a) bring an individual action in small claims court; (b) pursue an enforcement action through the applicable federal, state, or local agency if that action is available; (c) seek injunctive relief in a court of law in aid of arbitration; or (d) to file suit in a court of law to address an intellectual property infringement claim.

 **16.3 Arbitrator**  
Any arbitration between you and Buffer will be settled under the Federal Arbitration Act and administered by the American Arbitration Association (“AAA”) under its Consumer Arbitration Rules (collectively, “AAA Rules”) as modified by these Terms. The AAA Rules and filing forms are available online at [www.adr.org](http://www.adr.org/), by calling the AAA at 1-800-778-7879, or by contacting Buffer. The arbitrator has exclusive authority to resolve any dispute relating to the interpretation, applicability, or enforceability of this binding arbitration agreement.

 **16.4 Notice of Arbitration; Process**  
A party who intends to seek arbitration must first send a written notice of the dispute to the other party by certified U.S. Mail or by Federal Express (signature required) or, only if that other party has not provided a current physical address, then by electronic mail (“Notice of Arbitration”). Buffer’s address for Notice is: Buffer, Inc., 2443 Fillmore Street #380-7163, San Francisco, CA 94115. The Notice of Arbitration must: (a) describe the nature and basis of the claim or dispute; and (b) set forth the specific relief sought (“Demand”). The parties will make good faith efforts to resolve the claim directly, but if the parties do not reach an agreement to do so within 30 days after the Notice of Arbitration is received, you or Buffer may commence an arbitration proceeding. During the arbitration, the amount of any settlement offer made by you or Buffer must not be disclosed to the arbitrator until after the arbitrator makes a final decision and award, if any. If the dispute is finally resolved through arbitration in your favor, Buffer will pay you the highest of the following: (i) the amount awarded by the arbitrator, if any; (ii) the last written settlement amount offered by Buffer in settlement of the dispute prior to the arbitrator’s award; or (iii) $10,000.

 **16.5 Fees**  
If you commence arbitration in accordance with these Terms, Buffer will reimburse you for your payment of the filing fee, unless your claim is for more than $10,000, in which case the payment of any fees will be decided by the AAA Rules. Any arbitration hearing will take place at a location to be agreed upon in Santa Clara County, California, but if the claim is for $10,000 or less, you may choose whether the arbitration will be conducted: (a) solely on the basis of documents submitted to the arbitrator; (b) through a non-appearance based telephone hearing; or (c) by an in-person hearing as established by the AAA Rules in the county (or parish) of your billing address. If the arbitrator finds that either the substance of your claim or the relief sought in the Demand is frivolous or brought for an improper purpose (as measured by the standards set forth in Federal Rule of Civil Procedure 11(b)), then the payment of all fees will be governed by the AAA Rules. In that case, you agree to reimburse Buffer for all monies previously disbursed by it that are otherwise your obligation to pay under the AAA Rules. Regardless of the manner in which the arbitration is conducted, the arbitrator must issue a reasoned written decision sufficient to explain the essential findings and conclusions on which the decision and award, if any, are based. The arbitrator may make rulings and resolve disputes as to the payment and reimbursement of fees or expenses at any time during the proceeding and upon request from either party made within 14 days of the arbitrator’s ruling on the merits.

 **16.6 No Class Actions**  
YOU AND BUFFER AGREE THAT EACH MAY BRING CLAIMS AGAINST THE OTHER ONLY IN YOUR OR ITS INDIVIDUAL CAPACITY AND NOT AS A PLAINTIFF OR CLASS MEMBER IN ANY PURPORTED CLASS OR REPRESENTATIVE PROCEEDING. Further, unless both you and Buffer agree otherwise, the arbitrator may not consolidate more than one person’s claims, and may not otherwise preside over any form of a representative or class proceeding.

 **16.7 Modifications to this Arbitration Provision**  
If Buffer makes any future change to this arbitration provision, other than a change to Buffer’s address for Notice of Arbitration, you may reject the change by sending us written notice within 30 days of the change to Buffer’s address for Notice of Arbitration, in which case your account with Buffer will be immediately terminated and this arbitration provision, as in effect immediately prior to the changes you rejected will survive.

 **16.8 Enforceability**  
If Section 16.6 is found to be unenforceable or if the entirety of this Section 16 is found to be unenforceable, then the entirety of this Section 16 will be null and void and, in that case, the parties agree that the exclusive jurisdiction and venue described in Section 17.1 will govern any action arising out of or related to these Terms.

### 17\. General Terms

These Terms, together with the Privacy Policy and any other agreements expressly incorporated by reference into these Terms, are the entire and exclusive understanding and agreement between you and Buffer regarding your use of the Service. You may not assign or transfer these Terms or your rights under these Terms, in whole or in part, by operation of law or otherwise, without our prior written consent. We may assign these Terms at any time without notice or consent. The failure to require performance of any provision will not affect our right to require performance at any other time after that, nor will a waiver by us of any breach or default of these Terms, or any provision of these Terms, be a waiver of any subsequent breach or default or a waiver of the provision itself. Use of section headers in these Terms is for convenience only and will not have any impact on the interpretation of any provision. Throughout these Terms the use of the word “including” means “including but not limited to”. If any part of these Terms is held to be invalid or unenforceable, the unenforceable part will be given effect to the greatest extent possible, and the remaining parts will remain in full force and effect.

 **17.1 Governing Law**  
These Terms are governed by the laws of the State of California without regard to conflict of law principles. You and Buffer submit to the personal and exclusive jurisdiction of the state courts and federal courts located within Santa Clara County, California for resolution of any lawsuit or court proceeding permitted under these Terms.

 **17.2 Consent to Electronic Communications**  
By using the Service, you consent to receiving certain electronic communications from us as further described in our Privacy Policy. Please read our Privacy Policy to learn more about our electronic communications practices. You agree that any notices, agreements, disclosures, or other communications that we send to you electronically will satisfy any legal communication requirements, including that those communications be in writing.

 **17.3 Contact Information**  
The Service is offered by Buffer, Inc. located at 2443 Fillmore Street #380-7163, San Francisco, CA 94115. You may contact us by sending correspondence to that address or by emailing us at [hello@buffer.com](mailto:hello@buffer.com). You can access a copy of these Terms by clicking here: [buffer.com/legal#terms](http://buffer.com/legal#terms)

 **17.4 Notice to California Residents**  
If you are a California resident, under California Civil Code Section 1789.3, you may contact the Complaint Assistance Unit of the Division of Consumer Services of the California Department of Consumer Affairs in writing at 1625 N. Market Blvd., Suite S-202, Sacramento, California 95834, or by telephone at (800) 952-5210 in order to resolve a complaint regarding the Service or to receive further information regarding use of the Service.

 **17.5 International Use**  
Access to the Service from countries or territories or by individuals where such access is illegal is prohibited

## Privacy Shield Policy

Buffer Inc. (“Buffer”) complies with the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework and the Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework (the “Frameworks”) as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of Personal Information (as defined below) that is transferred from the European Economic Area (“EEA”), the United Kingdom and/or Switzerland, to the United States in reliance on Privacy Shield. Buffer has certified to the Department of Commerce that it adheres to the Privacy Shield Principles (the “Principles”) with respect to such information.

If there is any conflict between the terms in this privacy policy and the Principles, the Principles will govern. To learn more about the Privacy Frameworks, and to view our certification, please visit <https://www.privacyshield.gov/>.

This Privacy Shield Policy supplements our Privacy Policy. Capitalized terms used in this Privacy Shield Policy have the meaning given to them by our Privacy Policy, unless specifically defined in this Policy. In case of conflict between our Privacy Policy and this Policy with regard to our privacy practices under the Frameworks, this Policy prevails. This Policy applies to Buffer, which is subject to the investigatory and enforcement powers of the Federal Trade Commission.

 **Personal Information Received from the European Economic Area & Switzerland**  
Buffer may receive from the EEA and Switzerland some or all of the information listed in our Privacy Policy. Some of that information may qualify as “personal information” or “personal data” (collectively, “Personal Information”) as defined in the Principles. To the extent that Buffer receives Personal Information from the EEA and Switzerland in reliance on the Frameworks, Buffer will handle such Personal Information in accordance with the Principles.

 **How We Obtain Personal Information**  
We obtain and process Personal Information in different capacities.

As a data controller, we collect and process Personal Information from the EEA and Switzerland when offering our products and services to individuals as set forth in our Privacy Policy.

As a data processor, we process Personal Information from the EEA and Switzerland on behalf of our commercial customers when providing our B2B products and services. In that context, we only process Personal Information on behalf of and at the direction of our commercial customers (which are data controllers), as explained in the Privacy Policy.

For all types of processing, Buffer commits to the Principles of the Privacy Shield with respect to all Personal Information received from the EEA and Switzerland in reliance on the Frameworks.

 **Notice**  
We provide information regarding our privacy practices in our Privacy Policy.

When we process Personal Information on behalf of our commercial customers, our commercial customers determine the categories of data they provide to our Service and the purposes of the processing. Accordingly, our commercial customers are responsible for providing notice to individuals and you should review their privacy policies for more information regarding their data processing practices.

 **Data Integrity and Purpose Limitation**  
Buffer may use the Personal Information it receives from the EEA and Switzerland for the purposes set forth in our Privacy Policy or as you may otherwise be notified. We take reasonable steps to ensure that the Personal Information we process is reliable for its intended use, accurate, complete, and current to the extent necessary for the purposes for which we use the Personal Information. We will not process Personal Information in a way that is incompatible with the purposes for which it has been collected or subsequently authorized by you. We will adhere to the Principles for as long as we retain the Personal Information collected under the Frameworks.

 **Onward Transfers**  
Our Privacy Policy describes the circumstances in which we may disclose your information to third parties. We remain responsible for the processing of Personal Information received under the Frameworks and subsequently transferred to a third party acting as an agent if the agent processes such Personal Information in a manner inconsistent with the Principles, unless we prove that we are not responsible for the event giving rise to the damage. We may be required to disclose Personal Information in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements.

 **Data Security**  
We use reasonable and appropriate measures to protect your Personal Information from loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction, taking into account the risks involved in the processing and the nature of the Personal Information.

 **Choice**  
We will give you an opportunity to choose whether your Personal Information may be used for a purpose that is materially different from the purposes for which it was originally collected or subsequently authorized by you, or if we intend to disclose it to a third party acting as a data controller that we have not previously disclosed to you. In such circumstances, we will notify you and offer you the opportunity to opt-out of such uses and/or disclosures where non-sensitive Personal Information is involved, and to opt-in where sensitive Personal Information is involved.

 **Access to Personal Information**  
Where appropriate, Buffer will provide you with access to the Personal Information that we maintain about you. Buffer will also correct, amend or delete Personal Information that we maintain about you when it is inaccurate or has been processed in violation of the Principles and you send a written request to us using the information provided in the “Contact Information” section below. We will review your request in accordance with the Principles, and may limit or deny access to Personal Information where providing such access is unreasonably burdensome or expensive under the circumstances, or as otherwise permitted by the Principles.

When we process Personal Information on behalf of our commercial customers, our commercial customers control the type of information we obtain, how that information is used and disclosed, and how it can be modified. Accordingly, if you wish to request access, limit use or disclosure of your Personal Information, please contact us using the information provided in the “Contact Information” section below.

 **Recourse and Enforcement**  
We conduct an annual self-assessment of our Personal Information practices to verify that the attestations and assertions made in this Policy are true and have been implemented as represented.

If you have any questions or concerns, we encourage you to write to us at the address listed below. We will investigate and attempt to resolve any complaints or disputes regarding our use and disclosure of Personal Information in accordance with the Principles. Within the scope of this privacy notice, if a privacy complaint or dispute cannot be resolved through Buffer, Inc.’s internal processes, Buffer, Inc. has agreed to participate in the [VeraSafe Privacy Shield Dispute Resolution Procedure](https://www.verasafe.com/privacy-services/dispute-resolution/privacy-shield-dispute-procedure/), which serves as our third-party non-profit alternative dispute resolution provider located in the United States and operated by VeraSafe. Subject to the terms of the VeraSafe Privacy Shield Dispute Resolution Procedure, VeraSafe will provide appropriate recourse free of charge to you. To file a complaint with VeraSafe under the Privacy Shield Dispute Resolution Procedure, please submit the required information to VeraSafe here: <https://www.verasafe.com/privacy-services/dispute-resolution/submit-dispute/>. For residual complaints not fully or partially resolved by other means, you may be able to invoke binding arbitration as detailed in the Principles.

 **Privacy Shield Policy Changes**  
This Policy may be changed from time to time, consistent with the requirements of the Frameworks. You can determine when this Policy was last revised by referring to the “Last Updated” legend at the bottom of this Policy. Any changes to this Policy will become effective when posted to our website.

 **Contact Information**  
If you have questions, concerns, or complaints about this Privacy Shield Policy or Buffer’s privacy practices, or if you would like to exercise your rights and choices with regard to your Personal Information, please contact us by email at [hello@buffer.com](mailto:hello@buffer.com) or write to us at the following address:

Buffer Inc  
2243 Fillmore St #380-7163  
San Francisco, CA 94115  
United States

If you have any thoughts or questions about this Privacy Policy please [let us know](mailto:hello@buffer.com).

 _Last updated: July 29, 2019_

## Security

### Reporting an issue

We know how much work goes in to pen testing! To avoid frustration, you can check out these [common non-vulnerabilities](https://sites.google.com/site/bughunteruniversity/nonvuln) that don't qualify for rewards.

Got a valid issue? Awesome! Please include:

  * A summary of the problem
  * A severity rating of 1 - 5 (1 being least severe, 5 being most ie. you can easily hijack, impersonate or access any other account or data)
  * A PoC or breakdown of how to replicate the issue
  * The operating system name and version as well as the web browsers name and version that you used to replicate the issue

Please email any issue you'd like to report to [security@buffer.com](mailto:security@buffer.com)

### GPG Encryption

If you plan to provide access tokens, secure cookies or sensitive data/logs as an example, we kindly ask you to let us know and we will provide our GPG public key to you.

### Rewards

We're eternally grateful for all of those who put in hard work to identify weaknesses within Buffer. For reports that are not [common non-vulnerabilities](https://sites.google.com/site/bughunteruniversity/nonvuln), we like to reward those who responsibly disclose vulnerabilities with an acknowledgement, swag or bounty money.

### Acknowledgements

We appreciate the work that goes into finding and disclosing security flaws in Buffer and would like to thank the following individuals and organizations:

  * Sakurity - [Security Consulting](http://www.sakurity.com/)

We've been working closely with Egor and his team at Sakurity to identify key weaknesses within our app. They've continuously proven to be experts in identifying OAuth weaknesses. They have helped us identify and resolve potential security holes such as account hijacking, access token leaks, XSS and CSRF exploits.

  * [Scott Arciszewski](https://twitter.com/voodookobra) & [Taylor Hornby](https://twitter.com/defusesec)
  * KoF2002 & Sr33h4r
  * Mygapu Vandana
  * MD MIHIR MISTRY
  * Apoorv Joshi
  * Satheesh Raj
  * Arbin Godar
  * Swapneil Dash

## Join 75,000+ growing businesses that use Buffer to build their brands

Get started now
